# ANDRÉ LISBOA

UI/UX Designer



#### **PROFILE**

Hi, my name is André Lisboa and I've been working as a UI/UX designer since 2015. Throughout my professional journey, I've worked in several companies focusing on digital products. I provide all the necessary demands of a UI designer, with emphasis on design systems, handoff for development, structuring of interfaces, as well as visual design.

In addition, I have been working as a UI/UX teacher on the Alura platform since 2018. I have launched 19 courses and over 15,000 students have accessed them in the last 6 months.

#### CONTACT

al.andrelisboa90@gmail.com

+55 (21) 99385-3311

São Paulo - SP

#### **SKILLS**

UI/UX Design; Design Systems; Visual design; Responsive design; User testing; Handoff for devs

#### **EDUCATION**



Visual Design

PUC-Rio

2011-2015

#### **LANGUAGES**



Portuguese

**Native** 



English

**Fluent** 



Spanish

**Can communicate** 



Learning

#### **EXPERIENCE**



## UI/UX Teacher

Alura Online Courses

Since 2018

Since 2018, I have been teaching UI design at the Alura course school. I have launched 19 courses with themes that explore the world of UI and UX.

## **UI** Designer

Fluency Academy

2022-2023

Between 2022 and 2023, I worked at Fluency as a Senior UI Designer. My goal was to evolve the brand's products with UI design.

## **UI** Designer

Afinz Bank

2021-2022

My main objective with the company was the construction of the design system, along with the creation of flows and functionalities.

#### UI/UX Designer

Super Revendedores

2018-2020

At Super Revendedores, I was responsible for the entire creation and evolution of the platform in terms of design. I was responsible for creating new journeys and flows for the system, which existed on the website, iOS, and Android.

## UI/UX Designer

2016-2018

My first experience as a graduated UI designer, I was responsible for the evolution of the Sunset corporate events application.